
export const QUESTIONS = [

    {
        question: 'How long have you not planted a tree?',
        answer: ["One month or less","Six months or more","I never planted"," I never planted but I want to plant"],
        points: [100,50,0,25]
    },
    {
        question: 'Your diet today was based on?',
        answer: ["Organic vegetables and vegetables","Meat and processed foods","Transgenic vegetables and vegetables","I am not interested in the origin of my food"],
        points: [100,50,0,25]
    },
    {
        question: 'What was your mode of transportation to go to work/school today?',
        answer: ["Bicycle","Bus","Car ","Subway"],
        points: [100,50,0,25]
    },
    {
        question: 'Do you know how many people die each year from air pollution?',
        answer: ["100 thousand people","1 million people","7 million people","100 million people"],
        points: [100,50,0,25]
    },
    {
        question: 'Do you know how much it costs per year to manage damage from fires?',
        answer: ["30 million dollars ","From 64 to 256 billion dollars","From 50 to 60 billion dollars","From 50 to 60 billion dollars"],
        points: [100,50,0,25]
    },
    {
        question: 'How much of your homes electrical energy comes from renewable sources?',
        answer: ["0%","Up to 25%","Up to 50%","75% or more"],
        points: [100,50,0,25]
    },
    {
        question: 'Do you know how much it costs per year to manage damage from fires?',
        answer: ["30 million dollars ","From 64 to 256 billion dollars","From 50 to 60 billion dollars","From 50 to 60 billion dollars"],
        points: [100,50,0,25]
    },
    {
        question: 'How much of your homes electrical energy comes from renewable sources?',
        answer: ["0%","Up to 25%","Up to 50%","75% or more"],
        points: [100,50,0,25]
    },
    {
        question: 'Do you know how much it costs per year to manage damage from fires?',
        answer: ["30 million dollars ","From 64 to 256 billion dollars","From 50 to 60 billion dollars","From 50 to 60 billion dollars"],
        points: [100,50,0,25]
    },
    {
        question: 'How much of your homes electrical energy comes from renewable sources?',
        answer: ["0%","Up to 25%","Up to 50%","75% or more"],
        points: [100,50,0,25]
    },
]